Alvan

SOFTWARE ENGINEER



EDUCATION

Harbin Institution of Technology – Bachelor, Computer Science, 2015-2019

SKILLS

- Languages : <u>Solidity | JavaScript(TypeScript) | Move | Rust</u>
- Fields: Smart Contract | EVM | DeFi (Dex,Lending,Restaking and etc) | theGraph

EXPERIENCE

SOFTWARE ENGINEER, NEO 2021-PRESENT

- > Developed smart contracts for a over-collateralized lending protocol.
- > Developed smart contracts for a leveraged yield farming protocol.
- > Developed smart contracts for a composable Nft protocol on Neo.
- > Developed smart contracts and backend for a lottery blind box project on Aptos and Sui.
- > Developed smart contracts and subgraph for a launchpad project.
- > Developed smart contracts and subgraph for a pumpfun-like project.
- > Assisted in the development of the zk interoperable component for Neo blockchain.
- > Assisted in the development and testing of the bridge contracts for Neox blockchain.
- > Achieved 6th place in the SUI Move CTF.

SOFTWARE ENGINEER, CHINA'S INDUSTRIAL BANK 2019-2020

> Developed backend for credit card system.

PROFILE

I am a Smart Contract Engineer with extensive experience in Solidity, Hardhat, Foundry, and other blockchain toolchains. I have a deep understanding of EVM and am familiar with the economic models of mainstream DeFi projects.

I am capable of building corresponding off-chain programs and excel at quickly learning and developing on new public chains. I have knowledge of Move and have developed projects on Aptos and SUI, participating in hackathons. In addition, I have an understanding of ZK and have participated in related development. My ability to quickly adapt to new technologies and my dedication to staying at the forefront of blockchain technology make me a strong candidate for challenging and innovative projects.

Links

Github: https://github.com/passer-byzhang

website: https://alvan.coffee/

TG: t.me/AlvanZhang

e-mail: 19970216zhang@gmail.com

phone: 15568520958

wechat: zy122402